usa.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy : USA.com

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE. World Media Group, LLC ("Company") and USA.com ("the Website") (collectively "we") are committed to protecting the privacy and security of our customers and visitors on the Website. This Privacy Policy sets forth how the Website collects and uses personal information. By using this Website, you acknowledge that you have read and accepted our privacy practices set forth below.

If you do not accept our privacy practices, then you should not continue to use this Website. This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into and forms part of our Terms of Use.

**1\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect personally identifiable information sent to our Website, both during transmission and afterwards.

However, despite our efforts to maintain the confidentiality and security of your personal information, no method of transmission over the Internet and no method of electronic storage is completely secure. Although we make every effort to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION WE WILL COLLECT**

We may collect the IP address of your computer in order to enable us to detect unauthorized transactions and to better manage website traffic. We also may collect non-personal information from you such as the type of browser that you use or your connection speed.

We may also use "cookies," which are small data files placed and stored on your computer, to help you manage your use of our Website. Cookies are used as follows:

  1. To recognize you as a regular user;
  2. To remind us of who you are;
  3. To customize our Website and enhance visitor satisfaction;
  4. To estimate our audience size by determining repeat usage of the Website to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior;
  5. To track your progress;
  6. To measure traffic patterns for use as a research tool to understand how our users habits are similar or different from one another; and
  7. To conduct other research.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, in order to give you the chance to determine whether or not to accept it. If you do not accept cookies, some pages of this Website may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information.

**3\. PURPOSES FOR WHICH WE WILL USE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We make every effort to identify the purposes for which we will collect personal information at or before the time the information is collected. We will use your personal information only for the purposes disclosed at the time of collection or as otherwise set out in this Privacy Policy, unless we have your consent for another use, or unless such other use is authorized or required by law.

Our policy is to collect personal information from you for the following purposes:

  1. to personalize our Website so that it is most useful to you;
  2. to allow you to log into our Website automatically each time you visit, rather than requiring you to manually type your name and password each time;
  3. to maintain a commercial relationship with you and to communicate with you (which may include providing services, advertising, and promotions);
  4. to request your feedback on our Website;
  5. to meet legal and regulatory requirements;
  6. to offer you more targeted and relevant services or promotions directly or on behalf of our partners,
  7. to administer, maintain, and manage our business operations; and
  8. as otherwise required by law.

**4\. SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

This Website does not rent, trade, or share personal information with third parties, except when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  1. We may share your personally identifiable information with our affiliated companies;
  2. We may share your information with third parties in order to improve the quality or design of the Website, and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking and analyzing user preferences and trends;
  3. We may share your personal information if required by law and if we believe that the disclosure is required or necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial processing or legal process served on our Website;
  4. We may share personal information if we believe that it is required in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, a potential threat to the physical safety of a third party, or as otherwise required by law;
  5. We may transfer personal information to a third party entity in the event of an assignment of this Website for any reason;
  6. We may share personal information with our legal, financial, and other professional advisors;
  7. We may share personal information with website developers in the event that we are upgrading or improving our Website; and
  8. We may share personal information with third parties upon receiving your consent as required by law.

Except as provided above, we will not share any of your information to any third party without permission.

**5\. ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You can review, update, delete, or correct your personal information that you have provided to us. To access your personal information, we require a written request;. Upon receipt of any written request, we will take commercially reasonable steps to provide you with the opportunity to access any such information.

**6\. EMAIL REQUESTS FOR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If you ever believe that you have been a victim of fraud, please report it to the police and take all available actions to protect yourself. Also, please notify us, so that we can take all possible actions to protect you and the other users of this Website.

**7\. CHILDREN**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. In furtherance of this commitment, we restrict the use of our Website to persons eighteen (18) years of age or older. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13).

**8\. CONTACT WITH YOU**

We may use your email address to contact you from time to time, in order to send notices required by law and to provide information regarding this Website. We reserve the right to mail or email information to you about our services, to provide offers to customers, or to send out a newsletter or other mailing to you. You may at any time choose to unsubscribe (or "opt-out") of any of our mailings, either by adjusting your membership settings or by contacting us.

**9\. CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time at our sole discretion and without prior notice. If we make any material amendments, we will advise you about those changes by notifying you in a prominent place on our Website. You should check back with us from time to time in order to confirm that there have been no significant changes.

Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the Privacy Policy then in effect at the time of use.

**10\. OTHER LEGAL NOTICES**

If you ever have a dispute over privacy or security, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. We will always make every effort to resolve any concerns that you have regarding privacy that arises in connection with this Privacy Policy.

**11\. CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

If you are a California resident, you have the right to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of your personal information with third parties for their own direct marketing uses. California law provides that you have the right to submit a request to us at our email address in order to receive information on the categories of customer information that we shared and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information during the prior calendar year. To obtain this information, please contact us and inlcude "Request for California Privacy Information" in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you in your email address in response.

Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

**12\. CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or concerns over this Privacy Policy or if you need further information regarding the access to your personal information, or how your personal information is used, you may contact us.

**13\. EFFECTIVE DATE**

This Privacy Policy was last modified on the 29th of March, 2011.
